"Double Helix"
The wedding is set to be held in Paris.
You absolutely must come.
Have you set the date yet?
It should be finalized in
the next couple of days.
But lately, Wen Shichen...
seems to have developed
pre-wedding anxiety.
Even though he doesn't say it,
I can feel it.
He's incredibly nervous.
He's even worried you'll
come and steal me away.
Then he really needs to watch out.
I might actually crash
the wedding and steal you.
I'd love nothing more.
I have to go.
He's coming over. Hanging up now. Bye!
Okay.
You're going to crash a wedding?
Why do you walk so quietly?
I was just joking.
Do you think that's funny?
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
I'm going to take a shower.
Well...
Mr. Lu has some
important matters to attend to lately.
So it might not be very
convenient for you to stay here.
Just...
What's up with Mr. Lu
these past couple of days?
He's even spacing out during meetings.
Looks like he's
overindulging in his love life.
Really?
I saw it myself.
These past few days,
he's been with that guy
who used to come to
the office looking for him.
They've been booking hotel rooms together.
Did you go to the same hotel too?
I...
(Episode 12: Together for a Lifetime)
I won't be going to work tomorrow.
Why?
You seem very busy,
and I can't really help you with anything.
I don't want to waste company resources.
Tomorrow, I'll arrange for someone
to have your desk moved back.
No need.
I...
It'll be quick, I promise.
It will definitely be moved tomorrow.
So just go back to work like a good boy.
Really, there's no need.
Go ahead with your work. I want to go...
Where do you want to go?
I'm sorry.
Go ahead and eat first.
I'll go take a shower.
I saw it myself.
These past few days,
he's been with that guy
who used to come to
the office looking for him.
They've been booking hotel rooms together.
Zhuo Lan's wedding
date is set for next month.
I want to go there early.
In what capacity are you going?
Won't you feel embarrassed going there?
How could you think that?
How else do you expect me to think?
You're her ex-husband.
You know what our relationship is.
We're just friends.
Friends?
I might believe that,
but others won't.
Lu Feng.
What's wrong with you lately?
Nothing is wrong with me.
I'm fine.
I've always been fine.
Can you please not go to her?
And after that,
don't have any contact with her ever again.
Lu Feng, you're hurting me.
I'm sorry.
What on earth is wrong with you lately?
I'm fine.
I've just been a bit busy.
Busy?
Do you still have time to book
hotel rooms with someone else?
With whom?
That guy from the restaurant the other day?
Did you really book a room with him?
Fine, let's do this.
From now on,
you can book rooms with whoever you want.
If you're lonely and
want a lover, go ahead.
Even if you get married, I don't care.
Do whatever you want.
What do you mean you
don't care if I get married?
What do you mean
it's fine if I find a lover?
Do you really care about me that little?
I'm sorry, Xiao Chen.
I didn't mean to.
Are you really going to see Zhuo Lan?
I don't agree to it.
You booked a room with someone else.
Did I agree to that?
He's a doctor.
A psychiatrist.
I'm really worried he'll leave me.
Back then, when his mother wanted
him to break up with me, he did.
Now, when his brother
tells him to leave, he leaves.
When his ex-wife tells
him to leave, he leaves.
He'll leave if anyone tells him to.
I'm really afraid that one day,
he'll suddenly walk away
and never come back.
Go to the hospital for a
comprehensive checkup.
See a psychiatrist.
That's impossible.
I can't be sick.
His name is Zhao Chi.
My sister introduced him to me.
Over the past few years,
whenever my emotions got unstable,
I would go to him for counseling.
He said
I have bipolar disorder
and kept telling me to go to the hospital.
I was too afraid to go.
Why didn't you go?
How could I have a mood disorder?
I love you so much.
I was afraid.
If I'm really sick,
you'll want me even less.
I was afraid
you'd think my love for you
was just because of my illness,
and not real.
Don't listen to his nonsense.
Whether you love me or not,
how could I not know?
It's not fake.
Really?
[Zhao Chi's contact infomration]
Hello.
I'm Cheng Yichen.
Can we meet?
You're awake.
Go freshen up and have breakfast.
Chou Cheng will be
here to pick you up soon.
Today,
you have a very important
meeting to attend.
Can't you come with me?
No.
Look at what a mess the house is.
I've called a cleaning
service to come over.
Don't worry.
I won't leave.
If you're really that worried,
my passport and ID are in the drawer.
You can take them with you.
Just focus on your meeting today.
About Zhao Chi,
we'll talk when you get back.
Okay?
Go to work and do a good job today.
Don't overthink things.
Go on.
I'll be waiting for you.
Doing this...
doesn't that violate patient privacy?
Showing it to the patient's family
doesn't count as a violation.
When I first met Lu Feng,
he had just started his own company.
He started staying awake all night.
I noticed
he had mild bipolar disorder.
As long as you weren't mentioned,
his condition was mostly manageable
with some simple counseling.
But since he came to Xincheng,
his condition has gotten worse each time.
I've known about you for a long time.
That day, I volunteered
to play the role of his lover.
I just wanted to see
the person who holds
the key to Lu Feng's heart,
and what you were like.
Did I disappoint you?
The fact that you came to see me
means you didn't disappoint me.
How can I help him?
Only you
can make him willing
to go to the hospital for treatment.
Then take me with you guys too.
It's too much trouble, and we don't
really hang out in the same circles anyway.
Yi-chen.
I want to borrow some money from you.
Lu Feng...
He's having some trouble.
[He's checking in with
Yichen, Yichen asks what's up]
[Lu Feng responds with "It's fine"]
Lu Feng.
Come somewhere with me.
I saved up some money myself,
and borrowed some from Yi-chen.
We'll sign the transfer
contract in a couple of days.
From now on,
this will be my home.
Your home?
Lu Feng.
I've been thinking.
We've known each other for over ten years,
and we've been entangled for just as long.
Now, you don't seem like yourself,
and I don't seem like myself.
This...
isn't what I wanted.
From now on,
let's just be friends.
You...
What on earth are you talking about?
Why can't I understand a single word?
Did I do something to make you unhappy?
Or...
are you worried about my illness?
Do you not want to be
with someone who's sick?
If you're sick, why won't
you go to the hospital?
With you like this,
how can I dare to be with you?
Now, there are only two paths left for me.
Either...
we never see each other again,
or...
I die by your hands.
Then let's never see each other again.
Brother.
How did Lu Feng suddenly get sick?
You want to buy a house,
and that's because of him too?
His illness...
requires him to rest in an environment
filled with beautiful memories.
That's why I want to buy this house.
I asked you all here today
because I need a favor.
He's sick,
but he refuses to go to the hospital.
I want to ask you guys
to help me force him to go to the hospital.
Yichen.
Actually...
Lu Feng is at the door.
Xiao Chen.
I'm sorry.
I broke your vase.
Give me the glass shards.
Let's go to the hospital.
Okay?
I'm not sick.
I'll go with you.
Okay?
I don't want you to see
me when I have an episode.
No matter what,
I will always stay by your side.
What if my illness
can't be cured?
Will you leave me?
No.
But if...
you don't get treatment,
I will definitely leave you.
What if I have an episode
and I hurt you?
What then?
Then you need treatment even more.
What if it can't be cured?
Then I'll...
go crazy with you.
Bipolar disorder.
Generally speaking,
it's just a glitch in the
brain's emotional switch.
Don't let the information online scare you.
This condition is completely manageable.
So what should I do?
Just cooperate with me.
Do you really have to leave in a bit?
Once I'm cured,
you won't leave me again, right?
Can't you stay with me?
No.
Dr. Zhao won't allow it.
Yichen.
I used to think you two were
just young and reckless,
not knowing how the world works,
thinking love conquers all.
Now you're in your thirties,
and yet, because of love,
you've driven yourselves to mental illness.
He's really something.
He will get better.
Leave the company to me.
I'll leave Lu Feng to you.
Yichen.
Thank you.
You don't need to thank me.
He's my family too.
I don't want to take my medicine right now.
I want to see Cheng Yichen.
- I want to see Xiao Chen.
- Mr. Lu...
Mr. Lu.
- Xiao Chen...
- I'm here.
- Mr. Lu...
- Xiao Chen.
Take your medicine first, Mr. Lu.
Xiao Chen.
Thank you.
Lu Feng.
I'm here to take you home.
The first person to study in a bar.
Shut up.
How cute.
He wants to go to grad
school for architecture.
That's really impressive.
Of course.
Bullshit.
For his ongoing condition,
you'll need to monitor him closely.
Besides making sure he
takes his medicine on time,
try to keep him in
a relatively peaceful and
stable home environment.
As for work,
avoid any intense arguments.
Okay, don't worry.
I'll keep that in mind.
Are you hungry?
Not really.
What do you want for dinner?
I want to eat...
the instant noodles you make.
Lu Feng.
Now that you're cured,
aren't you happy?
I am happy.
I haven't been this happy in years.
I can finally be with
you without any worries.
I'm so happy
that I don't even know what to do.
But you look
a bit unhappy.
Ever since I started
waiting for you this morning,
I kept telling myself
that I must show you
an incredibly happy face.
That way,
you'll feel at ease.
But I realized
I don't know what happiness looks like,
nor do I know
what kind of face to make.
Lu Feng, look.
Just like this.
We'll take it
one step at a time,
okay?
Why do you still keep this?
Close your eyes.
Love...
It moves people, but it hurts them too.
Look at you, getting all poetic.
Good thing I'm easygoing.
Otherwise,
I would've been driven
sick by you long ago.
Then should I thank you
for putting up with me all these years?
How are you going to thank me?
There are people here.
So what if there are?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm so happy, it feels like a dream.
How about now?
Now it feels even more like one.
From now on,
we will be very, very happy forever.
Lu Feng.
Xiao Chen.
Did you have a nightmare?
Lu Feng,
I had a dream.
What kind of dream?
I dreamed...
Your illness was never cured,
and then,
without saying a word,
you just died.
How could that happen?
Don't worry.
I would never leave
and die without telling you.
That was just a dream.
I'm going to live a very long life,
just as long as you.
Actually, I want to live longer than you.
Just by a little bit.
That way,
you won't be left all alone in this world,
and you won't have to feel that pain.
Xiao Chen.
From now on,
things will only get better for us.
Time to wake up!
Lu Feng.
Lu Feng!
What is it so early in the morning?
Lu Feng,
you've gotten so cute.
Me too.
It's been so long since
I've seen you this energetic.
It's just like
back when we were in school.
Well, look who's to blame for that.
If you let me be on top
every day from now on,
I promise I'll always be full of energy.
If
that's really what you want,
I suppose it's not out of the question.
Really?
If only
you were only this small,
how wonderful that would be.
I could just slip you into my pocket,
and wherever I go,
I could take you with me.
That way, I could see you
anytime I want.
What a coincidence.
I used to wish I could
shrink you down like that, too.
And then what?
Put you in my bag,
so that from then on,
I could always bring you along.
Then find a good spot
to put me in.
Wherever you go,
I'll follow.
How childish.
Thank you, thank you!
Bye-bye!
See? I told you he has a mind for business.
Where's your brother?
He should be at the airport by now.
Why didn't you go see him off?
Better not.
I'm afraid if I went,
I'd make a scene and try
to stop him from leaving.
So, from now on,
you plan to run this shop with Xiao Lo?
Yeah.
We're going to turn
it into a national chain
and take it public.
When that happens,
I'll take care of you.
Who needs you to take of me?
Lu Feng,
besides doing business,
what do you want to do most right now?
I don't know.
I just want to be with you.
Let me rephrase that.
Right now,
what do you want to do most?
Right now?
I want to go back to the past.
We really love your short videos!
Yeah, we do!
Thank you.
We came here straight after school.
Keep it up!
Can we take a photo together?
Sure, of course.
I guess we could.
Thank you so much!
No problem.
Give me a push.
Okay.
If you're not going to use
your eyes, donate them!
Forget it, forget it.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Fortune telling!
Career, marriage, I read it all!
Palmistry and face reading!
No charge if it's not accurate!
Guaranteed accuracy!
One reading to reveal your destiny!
Give me your hand.
Let me calculate...
In this life,
your path of love is full of obstacles.
All your life,
you'll be entangled with men.
And...
Hey, you haven't paid yet!
it will always be with the same man.
But though the road of love is winding,
true lovers will find their happy ending.
Really?
Thank you, Master.
Come on, let's go home.
Wait, I wasn't wrong!